

KHALED ABDELFATTAH YOUSSEF

Flutter Developer

About Me

Creative and knowledgeable Flutter Developer with solid background in Hamza. Solutions. Program systems using advanced languages. Improves performance consistently to meet changing demands. B. SC. in Computer Science passionate about Mobile Programming and problem-solving with a good experience in flutter development [Redux , Bloc , Provider , clean code, clean architecture]

Expertise Skill

MVVM

- Bloc
- clean architecture
- Redux

Solid

Firebase

- Git
- Data structure

Contact Me



+201010563335



🙀 ms3byoussef@gmail.com



https://ms3byoussef.github.io/ms3b-you/





https://gitlab.com/ms3byoussef



https://github.com/ms3byoussef



http://www.linkedin.com/in/ms3byoussef

Education

2013-2018

Faculty of Computing and Information | Mansoura University

Bachelor of Science (B.S.) - Information Systems

Work Experience

Mobile Application Developer | Hamza 2021 - NOW

> Hamza is a SOCIAL ENTERPRISE SOFTWARE HOUSE SOLUTION,

- Worked on making 10+ existing mobile responsive
- Developed 5+ cross-platform mobile apps
- Developed 3+ web apps and dashboard with flutte

Mobile Developer intern | Algoriza

2022 – 2022

Algoriza is a SOCIAL ENTERPRISE SOFTWARE HOUSE SOLUTION

- Developed 3 mobile applications.
- Learn Bloc & Flutter TDD Clean Architecture.

Frontend | Hamza

2019 - 2020

 Designing pages and working on setting up sales and management systems for some factories and shops.

PROJECTS

Perfect Salon

Flutter app for beauty salon in Kuwait.

Screens: https://2u.pw/OTPFdU

Cylinder

Flutter app for Cylinder gas Delivery application in Kuwait

- APK: https://2u.pw/tgbqPF
- Screens: https://2u.pw/MgPJKU

Nurseries of Kuwait

Flutter app for nurseries for Kids application

- APK: https://2u.pw/j9yKow
- Screens: https://2u.pw/nd8OZI

Aby Seyara

Flutter app for Car store

- APK: https://cutt.us/ThMaQ
- Screens: https://2u.pw/ldOn3S

booking

Flutter app for booking hotel for Algoriza internship

- APK: https://2u.pw/b9EyD8
- Video: https://2u.pw/P9LeuX

COURSES

- Design Patterns in Plain English |
 Mosh Hamedani Redux Tutorial .
- Udemy Flutter & Dart The Complete Guide [2021 Edition] (Maximilian) .
- Flutter & Dart The Complete Guide [Arabic Edition] .
- Flutter TDD Clean Architecture Course .
- Flutter Advanced Course Bloc and MVVM Pattern [Arabic][2023].
- Clean Architecture In Flutter 3 (Arabic).
- Clean Architecture In Flutter 3 (Arabic) .
- Udemy-The Complete 2020 Flutter Development Bootcamp with Dart (Angila).

Advanced projects

Lady Style

Flutter app for women's needs Saudi Arabia

- work with team in 3 apps (provider -employee-main app).
- web dashboard for Admin

School I

Flutter Web Site for E_learning

• web dashboard for Admin